Class of 1890 Records, 1886-1975
Smith College Archives
Class of 1890 Records
1886-1975
Smith College. Class of 1890.
RG 80 UUID:c15c5d7b-939f-496b-b2b2-34a26f888d8a
4 boxes (1 linear ft. and 8 linear inches)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains black and white photographs, letters, publications, questionnaires, class records, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1890.
The Class of 1890 was the twelfth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1890 Records contain materials describing the history of the Class of 1890. Types of materials include black and white photographs, letters, publications, questionnaires, class records, and memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1890.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1890 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Class of 1890: Baccalaureate 1890 (Box 1451, Folder 1)
- Class of 1890: Commencement 1890 (Box 1451, Folder 2)
- Class of 1890: Commencement Music 1890 (Box 1451, Folder 3)
- Class of 1890: Commencement Speaker 1890 (Box 1451, Folder 4)
- Class of 1890: Freshman Grind by 1889 1886 (Box 1451, Folder 5)
- Class of 1890: Groups 1886-89 (Box 1451, Folder 6)
- Class of 1890: Groups (Unidentified groups and individuals) 1887-88, other n.d. (Box 1451, Folder 7)
- Class of 1890: Ivy Day 1890 (Box 1451, Folder 8)
- Class of 1890: Junior Prom 1889 (Box 1451, Folder 9)
- Class of 1890: Officers 1886-90, 1892, 1895, 1900, 1905, 1910, 1915, 1920, 1925, 1930, 1935, 1940, 1948 (Box 1451, Folder 10)
- Class of 1890: Class Photo Book 1890 (Box 1451, Folder 11)
- Class of 1890: Questionnaires, Reunion 1920 (Originals) 1920 (Box 1451, Folder 12)
- Class of 1890: Questionnaires, Reunion 1920 (Copies) 1920 (Box 1451, Folder 13)
- Class of 1890: Questionnaires 1950? (Box 1451, Folder 14)
- Class of 1890: Class Letters 1891-1940 (Box 1451, Folder 15)
- Class of 1890: Smith Quarterly (Book) 1930-1940 (Box 1452)
- Class of 1890: Class Records (Book) 1886-90, 1892, 1895, 1900, 1905, 1910, 1915, 1920, 1925, 1930, 1935, 1940 (Box 1452)
- Class of 1890: Class Records 1948-56, 1958-61 (Box 1452, Folder 1)
- Class of 1890: Reunion 1910 (Box 1452, Folder 2)
- Class of 1890: Reunion 1920 (Box 1452, Folder 3)
- Class of 1890: Reunion 1925 (Box 1452, Folder 4)
- Class of 1890: Reunion 1930 (Box 1452, Folder 5)
- Class of 1890: Reunion 1940, 1950 (Box 1452, Folder 6)
- Class of 1890: Reunion 1945 (Box 1452, Folder 7)
- Class of 1890: Reunion Photographs 1905?, 1910?, 1940, 1950 (Box 1452, Folder 8)
- Class of 1890: Senior Dramatics ("Book of Job"- Music) 1890 (Box 1452, Folder 9)
- Class of 1890: Senior Dramatics ("Book of Job"- Programs, Review) 1890 (Box 1452, Folder 10)
- Class of 1890: Senior Dramatics (Photographs) 1890 (Box 1452, Folder 11)
- Class of 1890: Songs N.d. (Box 1452, Folder 12)
- Class of 1890: Sophomore Reception 1886 (Box 1452, Folder 13)
- Class of 1890: Class Supper 1890 (Box 1452, Folder 14)
- Class of 1890: Allen, Adaline White (Photographs, etc) 1941, other n.d. (Box 1453, Folder 1)
- Class of 1890: Barton, Alice 1944-45 (Box 1453, Folder 2)
- Class of 1890: Blodgett, Mattie Bacon 1893 (Box 1453, Folder 3)
- Class of 1890: Booth, Minnie Day (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1453, Folder 4)
- Class of 1890: Bowen, Fanny Corey (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1453, Folder 5)
- Class of 1890: Brown, Clara May (Photographs) (Box 1453, Folder 6)
- Class of 1890: Bufkin, Mary L. N.d. (Box 1453, Folder 7)
- Class of 1890: Burnham, Jessica (Photographs) 1886, 1896, 1900, 1966, other n.d. (Box 1453, Folder 8)
- Class of 1890: Carpenter, Mary Frances (Scrapbook) Various dates (Box 1453, Folder 9)
- Class of 1890: Cate, Carrie Quincy 1942 (Box 1453, Folder 10)
- Class of 1890: Cheever, Louisa Sewall (Box 1453, Folder 11)
- Class of 1890: Clark, Abigail Hinsdale 1945 (Box 1453, Folder 12)
- Class of 1890: Crandall, Regina Katharine 1891, 1940, other n.d. (Box 1453, Folder 13)
- Class of 1890: Cravath, Elizabeth Northway (Correspondence) 1942-43, 1953, other n.d. (Box 1453, Folder 14)
- Class of 1890: Cravath, Elizabeth Northway (Photographs) 1889, other n.d. (Box 1453, Folder 15)
- Class of 1890: Day, Harriet Burr (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1453, Folder 16)
- Class of 1890: Dodge, Caroline Louise (Photographs) 1889 (Box 1453, Folder 17)
- Class of 1890: Elmer, Edith 1889, 1899, 1903, 1910, 1919, 1924, 1928, 1935, 1938-40, 1945, 1975 (Box 1453, Folder 18)
- Class of 1890: Foley, Margaret Baker (Photographs, etc) 1921-22, 1930, other n.d. (Box 1453, Folder 19)
- Class of 1890: Goodale, Dora Read 1906-07, 1917, 1942 (Box 1453, Folder 20)
- Class of 1890: Greene, Anna Maria N.d. (Box 1453, Folder 21)
- Class of 1890: Hall, Anna Bond (Photographs) 1888 (Box 1453, Folder 22)
- Class of 1890: Hardwick, Rose Standish (Photographs, etc) 1896, 1912, 1915-16, 1939,, other n.d. (Box 1453, Folder 23)
- Class of 1890: Hoblitt, Margaret Smith (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 1)
- Class of 1890: Holt, Ellen 1886-87, 1920, 1940, 1957, 1960-61, other n.d. (Box 1454, Folder 2)
- Class of 1890: Holt, Ellen (Photographs) 1889, other n.d. (Box 1454, Folder 3)
- Class of 1890: Homans, Susan Manning 1933, 1953, other n.d. (Box 1454, Folder 4)
- Class of 1890: Huffman, Mary Lucy 1935 (Box 1454, Folder 5)
- Class of 1890: James, Gertrude (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 6)
- Class of 1890: Jenkins, Anna Spaulding (Box 1454, Folder 7)
- Class of 1890: Lamont, Lucy (Diary) 1886-1888 (Box 1454, Folder 8)
- Class of 1890: Lathrop, Anna Barrow (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 9)
- Class of 1890: Miner, Frances Manwaring 1886-87, other n.d. (Box 1454, Folder 10)
- Class of 1890: Moodey, Cornelia Chapin 1908 (Box 1454, Folder 11)
- Class of 1890: Phillips, Maud (Box 1454, Folder 12)
- Class of 1890: Robinson, Mary Clemant 1943 (Box 1454, Folder 13)
- Class of 1890: Seabury, Maria Elizabeth (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 14)
- Class of 1890: Sherrill, Ruth Dakin 1891 (Box 1454, Folder 15)
- Class of 1890: Sprague, Leonora Woodruff (Photographs) 1890 (Box 1454, Folder 16)
- Class of 1890: Sumner, Caroline Louise (Class notes, Bible Lectures) 1886-90 (Box 1454, Folder 17)
- Class of 1890: Sumner, Caroline Louise (Photographs) 1915, 1940, other n.d. (Box 1454, Folder 18)
- Class of 1890: Thayer, Mary Vining 1923, other n.d. (Box 1454, Folder 19)
- Class of 1890: Thomson, Lucy Doolittle (Photographs) 1889, 1943, other n.d. (Box 1454, Folder 20)
- Class of 1890: Walston, Louise (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 21)
- Class of 1890: Wiggin, Pauline Gertrude 1890 (Box 1454, Folder 22)
- Class of 1890: Willard, Mary Frances (Letters) 1888, 1890, 1916, 1961 (Box 1454, Folder 23)
- Class of 1890: Willard, Mary Frances (Photographs) N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 24)
- Class of 1890: Wilson, Ella May N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 25)
- Class of 1890: Wonson, Alice Manton N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 26)
- Class of 1890: Woodruff, Agnes Lloyd N.d. (Box 1454, Folder 27)